First, find out
what her interests are.
What does she like?
She likes action movies.
Just like Joey.
Is that the reason
you came back here, Peter?
Is she the one
you're trying to forget?
- May I buy something?
- What is it?
Four shampoos.
What are you laughing at?
Well, Peter is teaching me
how to impress girls.
Idiot.
You're trying to impress
our customer too?
I was just testing it.
It does looks effective.
Why are we stopping?
Ma'am, looks like
we've got a flat tire.
Our spare is broken.
I haven't had it fixed yet.
Stupid!
Berdugo is on his way.
He'll arrive early morning.
Everything is ready.
Do you still love her?
Actually, I love someone else
already...
Friends like you.
You love me already?
But aren't we just pretending?
There are some things...
you can't fake, Joey.
Is that why you're here
in Valmora, to forget?
That's the plan,
but it feels like
I can't escape it.
The two are gone.
Where's Andrew?
Even though my ex and I broke up
a long time ago,
it's hard to recover.
Tell me, are you
and Joey a couple?
Because I feel like
you're provoking me.
You're too close to Joey,
and I know you're doing it
to make me jealous.
- We're done, aren't we?
- I know.
I was the one who left,
the one who walked away,
and I regret it.
That's why I want you back,
Andrew.
[OBB]
Joey...
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Sorry, I feel embarrassed.
I disturbed you.
I thought something
bad happened to you.
You don't have to say sorry,
okay?
Yeah, that's true.
You have nothing
to do with this.
It's between me and Andrew.
[HEAVY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
I'll see you tomorrow, Clarissa?
- All right.
- Okay.
I'll just accompany mom
to her room.
I like her.
I hope she doesn't
give up easily.
Then be nice to her.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE RINGING]
I'm sorry.
The subscriber...
Clarissa...
Amazing.
Mom liked you.
You know, she wasn't like that
with her past caregivers.
Thank you, Ma'am.
Oh, what's wrong?
I was calling Joey
to share the good news.
But she's not answering
her phone.
Maybe she fell asleep.
It's already late anyway.
I'm sure when you talk to her,
she'll be happy about your news.
Everything's going to be okay,
Clarissa,
even your husband's situation.
Just have faith.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Yes, Ma'am.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[DAUNTING MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey!
What are you looking at?
Bro, looks like he wants
to beat us to the plan.
I don't intend to steal this.
I just want to know whose car
this is.
Idiot!
Are you trying to fool us?
Wait, Man.
I don't want trouble.
I have a family.
If you want to steal this car,
it's yours.
Enough talk!
Come on, hit him!
Yes, I have nothing to do
with your real relationship.
Joey...
Wait.
Are you jealous?
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
You and Andrew aren't together,
right?
Or are you starting to have
feelings for Andrew?
Me, jealous?
No way.
We're just pretending.
Andrew and I are just friends.
Well...
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
That's good.
That's good to know.
I just don't want anyone
to get hurt.
Especially now, it looks like...
Andrew and I have a chance
to fix our relationship.
I'm happy to hear that.
Don't worry about me.
I'm glad that you'll get back
together.
I'll go ahead
so you can talk more.
Good luck to both of you.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[STIRRING EMOTIONAL
MUSIC CONTINUES]
Andrew...
where were we?
Can we...
Let's talk about this later.
Our objective on why we're here
is more important.
Someone might see us.
[STIRRING EMOTIONAL
MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DAUNTING MUSIC PLAYING]
What are you doing?
[DAUNTING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [EXCLAIMS]
- [INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[THUDS]
[EXCLAIMS]
I said I don't want trouble!
[DAUNTING MUSIC PLAYING]
Boss, please don't kill us!
- Have mercy, Boss!
- Have some pity on us!
Here's the cellphone!
That's all we stole!
Just don't kill us, Boss!
I don't want to see
your faces here again, got it?
Yes, Boss! Let's go, Bro!
[INTENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
My companion got lost so...
I was going to bring this
to the room.
I'll return it to him.
I thought you left me.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
You were on the phone
for a long time.
I walked around.
And I think, you know what?
I'm getting drunk.
[CHUCKLES]
Are you trying to get me drunk?
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Just kidding.
I'm just kidding.
[CHUCKLES]
Excuse me,
I think I'm the one who's drunk.
I'm going to bed now.
Good night.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Actually, me too...
I still have boyfriend duties.
I need to clean up my stuff.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh, I don't have a key.
So annoying!
[GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
[ZOEY CHUCKLES]
You looked so sad earlier
when you were telling the story
about your ex.
But now, you can't wipe
the smile off your face.
I'm just happy I enjoyed
our date
under the stars.
Wait...
Maybe you're already
bored with me?
No.
I'm enjoying this too.
And this is my plan...
to have a good business,
so I won't have
to worry about money.
Just relax, because working all
the time is exhausting.
Speaking of work...
I have a question for you.
What is it?
Didn't you say
you own this resort,
but then your boss called you?
What's that? A different job?
Something like that.
What kind of work
do you do for him?
What are you doing here?
I don't have a key.
Key.
[LIGHT PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Can I talk to you?
I just want to explain
something.
Explain what?
There's nothing to explain.
Just don't give me false hope.
It's frustrating.
Give you false hope?
[PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING]
It's about the key!
I thought you were going
to give it to me.
But you don't want to,
you're just making me wait.
I want to go inside already.
I'm getting tired.
Okay, listen to me.
I didn't know...
Zoey would do that.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
You don't need to.
If you're getting back together,
then go ahead.
Right? If that makes you happy.
But that's not part of my plan.
Still, it could happen.
Right?
Why do you...
seem upset?
Maybe because I expected you
to be honest.
That you'll admit you still have
feelings for her.
But earlier you kept denying it.
You said you didn't.
But that's the truth.
I like someone else.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
You seem suddenly interested
in my work.
[CHUCKLES]
Nothing.
I'm just asking,
I'm just curious.
Maybe I can apply for a job
to your boss?
Or why don't you just
apply to me?
I'd hire you right away.
[SNICKERS]
What?
I could even make you
my personal assistant.
No, not with you.
We might end up with
a conflict of interest.
Better with your boss.
Right? Think about it.
What if I get in?
I might stay here
in Valmora for good.
Please.
Introduce me to him.
Because if I get in,
we'll be together longer.
All right, all right.
Tomorrow, I'll introduce you
to him.
For real?
[CHUCKLES]
Okay.
Cheers!
[CLINKS]
[DAUNTING MUSIC CONTINUES]
There you are!
How are my two love birds?
Auntie...
How's your dinner?
Really good.
Unique in a good way.
My boyfriend, Andrew,
really enjoyed it.
It even reached the other tent.
[DAUNTING MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's a pity I didn't catch you.
I even rushed because I really
wanted to hear your love story,
on how you met.
But, Auntie...
we're not leaving yet.
[DAUNTING MUSIC PLAYING]
What if we return the favor?
We'll treat you to dinner.
Oh, that's so sweet, dear,
but I have to decline.
Why? Are you leaving?
No, dear, because...
I have a very important meeting
tomorrow night,
and this meeting could expand
my business.
You know,
my beauty is high maintenance.
[CHUCKLES]
Yes.
Oh, my god.
The wine's all gone.
Can we order more?
[PHONE RINGING]
Oh, we could get another one,
but I might not be able
to join you.
What? Why?
I have something I need to do.
You're leaving me here alone?
Can I come with you?
Oh, how about this...
get another wine,
I'll just call Madam Delilah.
Then I'll come back, promise.
Don't bother.
I'll just go back to my room.
Wait, don't be mad.
You're not checking out yet,
right?
Okay, fine, how about this.
If you can't wait for me
later tonight,
let's meet again tomorrow?
[DAUNTING MUSIC PLAYING]
We'll have another date,
but different.
More romantic.
And then you'll leave me again?
No, not anymore.
Besides, I'm going to introduce
you to my boss, right?
If he likes you,
you'll work here.
We'll be together every day,
every night.
You won't have to leave.
Is that a promise?
I promise.
All right.
Okay.
I'll see you tomorrow.
[BRAZEN MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay, who else could it be?
You know, I'm sure it's Berdugo
who's meeting with Delilah.
Okay, Joey, now we know when.
What we need to know now
is where.
What if...
[DAUNTING MUSIC PLAYING]
We ambush Delilah tomorrow
to have breakfast with us?
That could work.
Right?
Or we could just follow her.
But it's Berdugo.
It's dangerous.
I'm sure his men are armed.
Could be.
I thought you weren't mad at me
anymore?
Why do you seem uninterested?
No, I'm just sleepy.
[DREAMY MUSIC PLAYING]
Sorry, I'm really tired.
Can we talk about this
tomorrow instead?
We still have plenty of time.
I'm really sleepy.
Of course.
Stay on the bed.
No, I won't.
You paid for this, right?
And you've already done so much
for our mission.
I'm fine on the sofa.
- I even prefer it.
- No, it's okay.
No, it's just the right size
for me, see?
[DREAMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Good night.
[BREATHES]
[SIGHS]
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR CLOSING]
[PHONE BEEPS]
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Wow, it's beautiful here!
- It's beautiful, isn't it?
Of course.
- Oh, wait.
- Yes?
- Let's take a picture.
- Okay, okay.
Smile.
[CAMERA SHUTTER SNAPS]
Why am I hurting?
We're not even together.
[EXHALES]
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
That's why I want you back,
Andrew.
[STIRRING EMOTIONAL
MUSIC PLAYING]
Why am I affected?
[STIRRING EMOTIONAL
MUSIC CONTINUES]
I don't want you anymore.
Will I really be happy
if we get back together?
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING EMOTIONAL MUSIC
CONTINUES]
You don't know how.
Admit it!
This is how it should be.
Then like this, see?
[STIRRING EMOTIONAL MUSIC
PLAYING]
[SPLASHES]
[STIRRING EMOTIONAL MUSIC
CONTINUES]
Now I know
what will make me happy.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
You, young people...
when you're not picked,
you think that's it,
it's like the end of the world.
I'll forget too.
That's not true.
Ma'am Delilah is expecting
- your arrival.
- Make sure...
nothing will go wrong tomorrow,
okay?
If something goes wrong
with this deal,
your Lumen-X will be history
in Valmora.
You are just a distributor.
Don't get too comfortable.
I'm not above hitting a woman!
What's going on with Sir Tomas?
No matter what he promises you,
do not take it.
Have you told him yet?
Dad, mom isn't here right now.
Joey, your father is alive?